cpclips.com 2018-12-11

# Privacy Policy | cpClips

**_Last updated_ **: July 10, 2016

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website cpClips.

By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you may not access the Service.

**_When and What information we collect_ : **

When providing feedback about our site, requesting support you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number, to respond to your request properly and improve overall experience.

Also while reporting bugs/problems your OS Name and Version Information, Browser Name and Version Information will be collected to help us eradicate the bug/problem.

**_Cookies_ : **

We use cookies to temporarily store information about video you are downloading to prepare the right download link for you. We clear that data as soon as you leave the website.

**_Third-Party Disclosure_ : **

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**_Third-party links_ : **

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**_How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?_ : **

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**_Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?_ : **

It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking.

**_Contact Us_ : **

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us at support@cpclips.com .
